Revenge gets ripped.
Love Lies Bleeding is a crime, romance, thriller film directed by Rose Glass.
Reclusive gym manager Lou falls hard for Jackie, an ambitious bodybuilder
headed through town to Las Vegas in pursuit of her dream.
But their love ignites violence, pulling them deep
into the web of Lou’s criminal family.
Lou, played by Kristen Stewart.
Jackie, played by Katy O'Brian.
Lou Sr., played by Ed Harris.
JJ, played by Dave Franco.
Beth, played by Jena Malone.
Daisy, played by Anna Baryshnikov.
Love Lies Bleeding is a 2024 romantic thriller film directed by Rose Glass from a screenplay she co-wrote with Weronika
Tofilska, and starring Kristen Stewart, Katy O'Brian, Jena Malone, Anna Baryshnikov, Dave Franco, and Ed Harris.
It is an international co-production between the
United Kingdom and the United States.
Set in 1989, the film's plot follows the lesbian relationship between a reclusive gym manager, who is estranged from her powerful father, a sinister
businessman with a criminal history, and an ambitious bodybuilder who gets wrapped up in the father's web of violence and coverups.
Love Lies Bleeding premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 20, 2024.
It was released theatrically in the United States by A24 on March 8, 2024,
and in the United Kingdom by Lionsgate UK on May 3, 2024.
The film received positive reviews from critics and was named one of the Top
Ten Independent Films of 2024 by the National Board of Review.
The film explores themes of homicide, blackmail, fbi, new mexico, eroticism.
The tone is intense and dark and thought_provoking.